# MUHAMMAD ZAHIRUDDIN



muhdzahir248@gmail.com



+60 149947806



Selangor, Malaysia

# **OBJECTIVE**

Adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience and speed.

### **EXPERIENCE**

July 2022 -September 2022

### Storekeeper

99 Speedmart SDN BHD · Filling the shelves

· Interacting with customers

April 2019 -May 2019

#### Cashier

Caltex Himpunan Jitu SDN BHD · Serve customers at the counter

· Clean the station area

### **EDUCATION**

2021 - Now

Bachelor Of Computer Science (Software Development) With Honours

Universiti Teknikal Malaysia Melaka

CGPA: 3.53 (Semester 3)

2019 - 2021

Science Stream

Kolej Matrikulasi Melaka

CGPA: 3.75

### **SKILLS**

HTML

**CSS** 

Javascript

C++

MySQL

**Bootstrap** 

# **LANGUAGES**

Malay

English